Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG 42.5
New York University Archives
Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center
Bulk, 1975-1997
1958-2012
RG 42.5
New York University Archives
55.0 boxes
The Grey Art Gallery and Student Center is NYU's art museum established in 1975 with the financial contribution from Abby Weed Grey. Building on the New York University's Art Collection, established in 1958, the gallery puts on exhibits of local, national and international interest. The collection consists of correspondence between the gallery and artists, lenders, funders, press and patrons; exhibit PR, catalogs, catalog drafts, exhibit labels, lists of items in exhibits, floor plans, research materials, grant applications; shipping, transporation, and insurance information.
47 Paige boxes; 8 flat boxes
Grey Art Gallery & Study Center.
New York University Art Collection.
Related Materials
Abby Weed Grey Papers
Grey Gallery Exhibition History
Technical Access Note
Collection contains a small number of audio cassettes and vhs tapes.
Separated Material
Photographs, slides, negatives, image transparencies and film from exhibitions have been moved to the University Photograph Collection. Floppy disks have been removed for migration. Annual reports of the New York University Art Collection have been moved to Alumni Associations and Activities.
Scope and Content
This collection documents the activities of the Grey Art Gallery and Student Center and its predecessor, the New York University Art Collection and was generated between 1958 and 2012. Among the more popular and unique exhibitions put on by the gallery are the Parviz Tanavoli exhibit of Persian art, sponsored by the Iranian government in honor of the American Bicentennial in 1976 and a series of exhibitions relating to AIDS in the late 1980s and early 1990s.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged in chronological order of the exhibits, except in the oversize series, where the arrangement is according to size.
The records have been arranged into four series:
Series I: Exhibition Files Series which contains, among others, gallery floor plans, exhibit labels, research materials from other institutions (including a small number of photographs and slides used for research but not for exhibition), correspondence with artists, patrons, collegues and potential donors, handwritten notes, press releases, clippings, pamphlets, brochures, invitations, catalogs, posters, postcards, memorundum, drafts, a small number of audio cassettes and transparencies.
Series II: Administrative Files Series is divided into four subseries.
Subseries A: Correspondence (1958-1977) contains thank you letters and other communications dealing with donations to the NYU Art Collection and the Grey Art Gallery.
Subseries B: Grey (1973-1980) contains correspondence, memorundum, notes, clippings, printed materials and other miscellaneous relating to the foundation of the Grey Art Gallery and its dealings with Abby Grey.
Subseries C: WNYC (1968-1973) consists of correspondence, drafts, notes and printed materials and other miscellanous of Ruth Bowman, the curator of the New York University Art Collection, and her involvement in a television and radio series: "Views on Art."
Subseries D: Development makes-up the majority of the administrative files and includes applications, rejections and acceptances for the NEH, NEA and NYSCA grants; loan agreements, rejected loans, lender information and correspondence; insurance certificates, shipping, delivery and transportation receipts and paperwork; condition reports, appeals for funds, funding sources and resumes.
Series III: Oversize contains items too large to fit into Series I, II and IV
Series IV: Publications contains printed catalogs and books used by the gallery.
Exhibition Files
Administrative Files
Oversize
Publications
Historical/Biographical Note
The Grey Art Gallery is New York University's fine arts museum whose function is to collect, preserve, study, document, interpret, and exhibit the evidence of human culture. the Grey distinguishes itself by emphasizing art's historical, cultural, and social contexts, with experimentation and interpretation as integral parts of programmatic planning. Thus, in addition to being a place to view the objects of material culture, the Gallery serves as a museum-laboratory in which a broader view of an object's environment enriches our understanding of its contribution to civilization.
The Grey Gallery and Student Center was inagurated on April 9, 1975 at 100 Washington Square East/33 Washington Place in the Silver Center building. Located on the site of the original New York University building (1835-1892), it was here that the nation’s first art department headed by Professor Samuel Morse was established. In 1927 Albert E. Gallatin, son of an NYU chemistry professor, established what is considered to be the first museum of modern art in the United States on the same site called the Gallery of Living Art. Later renamed Museum of Living Art, its collection consisted of contemporary paintings and drawings by creative and progressive artists. The museum was closed-down by the university in 1943 due to economic reasons.
In 1958 the New York University Art Collection was founded with the acquisition of Francis Picabia's "Resonateur" (ca.1922) and Fritz Glarner's "Relational Painting" (1949–50). Overseen by the NYU Art Committee headed by curator, Ruth Bowman, the collection continued to grow over the next decade and a half with the aid of alumni, artists and friends of the university. By the middle of the 1970s, the collection consisted of over 2000 paintings, sculptures, drawings, prints and photographs with heavy concentration in modern art, including works by such artists as Picasso, Leger and Hofmann. Many of the collection pieces were hung at separate locations throughout the university with new acquisitions being exhibited each year at the Contemporary Art Gallery of the Loeb Student Center. However, due to the lack of available space, most of the art work was kept in storage when not part of a special exhibition.
In 1974 Abby Weed Grey, a wealthy art collector and philanthropist, decided to donate one million dollars for the establishment of The Grey Art Gallery and Study Center. Most of the money went into renovating the 1st, 3rd and basement floors of the Silver Center building. The remaining funds were set aside as a permanent endowment for the maintenance, display and exhibition expenses of the collection, with the agreement that the university would cover basic operating expenses. Along with the financial contribution, Abby Grey also donated a large collection of Middle Eastern and Asian art which she had collected over the course of her life. This donation, combined with the New York University Art Collection, became the university's permanent collection housed in the newly established gallery. Mrs. Grey remained a frequent supporter of the gallery, giving another large donation in 1977 for the construction of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center Library of Fine Arts with the stipulation that selections from the Ben Abby Grey Foundation donated previously by her foundation would be exhibited in the library premises on a constant basis.
Upon its establishment, Grey Gallery was put under the authority of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences with Kenneth L. Mathis appointed its first director; Joy L. Gordon became the first curator. From inception, the Grey Gallery suffered from financial dificulties with many of its programs and exhibitions made possible due to extensive support by the National Endowment for the Arts, The National Endowment for the Humanities and the New York State Council for the Arts. The Gallery showcased large exhibitions in the main hall of the building with smaller exhibits staged in the small gallery and the gallery windows.
In the late 1970s the Grey Art Gallery was put under External Affairs alongside University Development, Press, Government and Community Relations. When External Affairs was disbanded in early 2000s, Grey Gallery stayed under University Development (UDAR) until being transferred under the Office of the Provost in the late 2000s.
Access Restrictions
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Loan agreements, insurance certificates, salary information and condition reports are permanently restricted. Contact the University Archives for details.
Provenance
The collection was transfered to the University Archives from the Grey Art Gallery in November of 2011, April 16, 2012 and June 2012.
Bowman, Ruth, 1923-; Gordon, Joy L.; Grey, Abbey Weed, 1902-1983; Littman, Robert R.; Mathis, Kenneth L.; Reynolds, Gary A.; Sokolowski, Thomas W.; Art museums |z New York (State) |z New York.; Art |x Study and teaching.; Artists.; Correspondence.; Ephemera.; Essays.; Exhibition catalogs.; Exhibitions.; Grant proposals.; Grey Art Gallery & Study Center.; Invitations.; Leaflets (printed works).; photocopies.; Posters.; Press releases.; Proposals.; Publications.; Receipts (financial records).; Registers (lists).; Research (document genres).; Research notes.
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-1988
  - Exhibition History Files, undated (Box I:1, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Grey's Tour, undated (Box I:1, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Copies, 1958-1971 (Box I:1, Folder 3)
  - Publicity -- NYU Publications, 1961-1964 (Box I:1, Folder 4)
  - Publicity Magazines (1 of 2), 1961-1967 (Box I:1, Folder 5)
  - Publicity Magazines (2 of 2), 1961-1967 (Box I:1, Folder 6)
  - Publicity - NYU (1 of 2), 1961-1971 (Box I:1, Folder 7)
  - Publicity - NYU (2 of 2), 1961-1971 (Box I:1, Folder 8)
  - Harold Rosenberg Articles (1 of 2), 1961-1971 (Box I:1, Folder 9)
  - Harold Rosenberg Articles (2 of 2), 1961-1971 (Box I:1, Folder 10)
  - Symposia (The Unpopular Artist in Popular Culture), 1962 December (Box I:1, Folder 11)
  - NYU Exhibition Catalogs (1 of 2), 1963-1968 (Box I:1, Folder 12)
  - NYU Exhibition Catalogs (2 of 2), 1963-1968 (Box I:1, Folder 13)
  - Exhibitions Sponsored By the NYU Art Collection, 1963-1973 (Box I:1, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition: Selections from the NYU Art Collection, 1963 March 6-20 (Box I:1, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition: Joseph Cornell, 1963 December 3-18 (Box I:1, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition: Bernard Childs, 1964 April 14-May 15 (Box I:1, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition of Paintings From the NYU Collection, 1964 September 14-October 9 (Box I:1, Folder 18)
  - Concrete Expressionism Exhibition, 1965 (Box I:1, Folder 19)
  - AFA Ancient Mexico Exhibit, 1965 January-March (Box I:1, Folder 20)
  - AFA -- A University Collects, 1965 June-1968 February (Box I:1, Folder 21)
  - Exhibition: Alumni Show, 1965 October 11-22 (Box I:1, Folder 22)
  - Exhibitions -- Recent Acquisitions, 1966 (Box I:1, Folder 23)
  - A Loan Exhibit from the NYU Collection (Gould Student Center), 1966 (Box I:1, Folder 24)
  - Sound Exhibition -- Loeb, 1966 March 4-18 (Box I:1, Folder 25)
  - Exhibition: Paul Brach, 1966 May 9-June 6 (Box I:1, Folder 26)
  - Form 99 Art Collection -- Picasso, 1966 August-November 1967 (Box I:1, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition: Contemporary Drawings, 1966 December 12-1967 January 6 (Box I:1, Folder 28)
  - Publicity -- A University Collects, 1966-1968 (Box I:1, Folder 29)
  - Aspects of American Realism, 1966-1976 (Box I:1, Folder 30)
  - Poem Paintings, 1967 January 9-February 5 (Box I:1, Folder 31)
  - Publicity, 1967 August-October (Box I:1, Folder 32)
  - NYU Art Exhibition Benefit, 1967 September (Box I:1, Folder 33)
  - Exhibition: Recent Acquisitions, 1967 September 15-October 9 (Box I:1, Folder 34)
  - The New York Painter (Marlborough-Gerson), 1967 September 27-October 14 (Box I:1, Folder 35)
  - Jean Tinguely -- "Man, Woman, Machine", 1967 December 11 (Box I:1, Folder 36)
  - Exhibition: Picasso Graphics, 1968 March 1-18 (Box I:1, Folder 37)
  - Selections from NYU Collection, 1968 April 27-May 4 (Box I:1, Folder 38)
  - 10th Anniversary of NYU Art Collection, 1968 September 9-October 2 (Box I:1, Folder 39)
  - Newsletters - Volume I-III, 1969-1972 (Box I:1, Folder 40)
  - Exhibition: Les Levine, 1969 January 20-February 20 (Box I:1, Folder 41)
  - Exhibition: Glassboro State College, 1969 October 1-31 (Box I:1, Folder 42)
  - Exhibition: Selections from NYU Art Collection, 1969 November 18-December 18 (Box I:1, Folder 43)
  - 100 Years of Impressionism (Wildenstein), 1970 April 2-May 9 (Box I:1, Folder 44)
  - Exhibition: Glassboro State College, 1971 April (Box I:1, Folder 45)
  - Hudson River/NYU Publicity, 1971 September-October (Box I:1, Folder 46)
  - 20th Century Painting and Sculpture from the NYU Art Collection, 1971 October 2-November 14 (Box I:1, Folder 47)
  - Exhibitions: University of Notre Dame, 1972-1973 (Box I:1, Folder 48)
  - Loeb Latin American Inst., 1972 September 14-October 5 (Box I:1, Folder 49)
  - Print Exhibition, 1973-1976 (Box I:1, Folder 50)
  - Exhibitions Print Show -- Hudson River Museum, 1973 January 13-March 4 (Box I:1, Folder 51)
  - Sandman Background Information, 1973 March-1977 July (Box I:1, Folder 52)
  - Selections from the NYU Art Collection -- University of Connecticut, 1973 March 12-April 15 (Box I:1, Folder 53)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition -- Loeb, 1973 June 13-August 9 (Box I:1, Folder 54)
  - Exhibitions: University of Connecticut (1 of 2), 1973 March 12-April 15 (Box I:1, Folder 55)
  - Exhibitions: University of Connecticut (2 of 2), 1973 March 12-April 15 (Box I:1, Folder 56)
  - Press for Gallery Opening -- Clippings (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box I:1, Folder 57)
  - Press for Gallery Opening -- Clippings (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box I:1, Folder 58)
  - Irish Directors of the 70s -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1975 (Box I:2, Folder 1)
  - Irish Directors of the 70s -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1975 (Box I:2, Folder 2)
  - Recent American Etching -- Photographs, 1975-1976 (Box I:2, Folder 3)
  - American Abstract Artists, 1975-1975 (Box I:2, Folder 4)
  - Prints and Technique Exhibition, 1975 February 10-1976 May 3 (Box I:2, Folder 5)
  - Poster Show -- "Images of an Era: The American Poster", 1975-1976 (Box I:2, Folder 6)
  - Poster Show Clipping File, 1975 November-1977 June (Box I:2, Folder 7)
  - Poster Exhibition -- PR, 1976 (Box I:2, Folder 8)
  - Poster Exhibition -- Invitations/Distribution, 1976 (Box I:2, Folder 9)
  - Poster Exhibition -- Shipping, 1976 (Box I:2, Folder 10)
  - Inaugural Exhibition -- Catalogue Copyright, 1975 April-1977 January (Box I:2, Folder 11)
  - Aspects of American Realism -- Clippings, 1976 January-March (Box I:2, Folder 12)
  - Prints and Techniques -- Press Releases, 1976 March 17 (Box I:2, Folder 13)
  - Prints and Techniques -- Clippings and Film File, 1976 March-April (Box I:2, Folder 14)
  - Video Festival, 1976 April-May (Box I:2, Folder 15)
  - Marjorie Strider BigBox PR, 1976 April 29-June 21 (Box I:2, Folder 16)
  - Parviz Tanavoli -- Locks from Iran Clipping File, 1976 February-December (Box I:2, Folder 17)
  - Parviz Tanavoli -- Bob's File, 1976 March 18-May 12 (Box I:2, Folder 18)
  - Locks Show (1 of 3), 1976 May-1977 January 12 (Box I:2, Folder 19)
  - Locks Show (2 of 3), 1976 May-1977 January 12 (Box I:2, Folder 20)
  - Locks Show (3 of 3), 1976 May-1977 January 12 (Box I:2, Folder 21)
  - Tanavoli, 1976 June 23-1977 January 13 (Box I:2, Folder 22)
  - Parviz Tanavoli, 1976 August 5-November 9 (Box I:2, Folder 23)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Clippings, 1976 June 10-1977 September 2 (Box I:2, Folder 24)
  - Udine Exhibition Correspondence, 1976 June 25-September 7 (Box I:2, Folder 25)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Memos, 1976 July-August (Box I:2, Folder 26)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Inviations, 1976 August 2 (Box I:2, Folder 27)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Checklists, 1976 August 11-27 (Box I:2, Folder 28)
  - Documentation -- Udine (1 of 2), 1976 August (Box I:2, Folder 29)
  - Documentation -- Udine (2 of 2), 1976 August (Box I:2, Folder 30)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman -- Clips, 1976 August 22-1978 January 19 (Box I:2, Folder 31)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman -- Checklist of Exhibition, 1977 February 1-March 4 (Box I:2, Folder 32)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy -- Essays by Christopher Scott, 1977 (Box I:2, Folder 33)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy -- Floor Plan, 1977 February-March (Box I:2, Folder 34)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman -- Invitations, 1977 February 1-March 4 (Box I:2, Folder 35)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Press Releases, 1976 September 2-14 (Box I:2, Folder 36)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Painting and Sculpture Clippings, 1976 September-October (Box I:2, Folder 37)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Works in Show, 1976 September-October (Box I:2, Folder 38)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Checklist, 1976 September-October (Box I:2, Folder 39)
  - Inaugural Exhibition Part II - Letters to Donnors and Artists, 1976 September-October (Box I:2, Folder 40)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Bob's File, 1941-1976 (Box I:2, Folder 41)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Clipping File, 1976 December-1977 May (Box I:2, Folder 42)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Invitations, 1976-1977 (Box I:2, Folder 43)
  - England [Beatrix Potter], 1976-1977 (Box I:2, Folder 44)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Hunt Institute and Other Miscellaneous, 1903-1977 (Box I:2, Folder 45)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Souvenir Catalog, 1977 (Box I:2, Folder 46)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Checklist, 1977 January-May (Box I:2, Folder 47)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Press Releases, 1977 March-May (Box I:2, Folder 48)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Horn Magazine Articles, 1929-1977 (Box I:2, Folder 49)
  - Circa 1776 -- Salute to Cooper-Hewitt Invitations, 1965-1976 (Box I:2, Folder 50)
  - Circa 1776 -- Press Releases, 1976 October 25 (Box I:2, Folder 51)
  - Grossman -- Bob's Notes, 1977 February (Box I:2, Folder 52)
  - Grosman -- Essay by Robert R. Littman, 1977 February (Box I:2, Folder 53)
  - Gallatin -- To Do, 1977 February 2-May 15 (Box I:2, Folder 54)
  - Gallatin -- Photographs, 1977 March-April (Box I:2, Folder 55)
  - Amnesty Poster Exhibition, 1977 March (Box I:2, Folder 56)
  - Panoramic Photography -- Hand List of the Exhibit, 1977 May-September (Box I:2, Folder 57)
  - Panoramic Photography -- Press Photos/Negatives, 1977 September (Box I:2, Folder 58)
  - Gallery of Living Art, undated (Box I:2, Folder 59)
  - Gallery of Living Art, undated (Box I:2, Folder 60)
  - Gallery of Living Art Revisited - Gallatin Questionnaires, 1977 May-September (Box I:2, Folder 61)
  - The Gallery of Living Art Revisited (1 of 2), 1978 November (Box I:2, Folder 62)
  - The Gallery of Living Art Revisited (2 of 2), 1978 November (Box I:2, Folder 63)
  - Exhibition: Sports Festival, circa 1970s (Box I:3, Folder 1)
  - Sam Wagstaff Photography Checklists, 1978 February 3-March 26 (Box I:3, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin Photographs, 1978 September-October (Box I:3, Folder 3)
  - New Deal for Art Newspaper Catalogue, 1977-1978 (Box I:3, Folder 4)
  - Changes in Perspective Essay, circa 1977-1978 (Box I:3, Folder 5)
  - Wilmarth/Sandman Essays, 1978 January 10-February 3 (Box I:3, Folder 6)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Henry J. Neils, 1957 May 28-1961 February 24 (Box I:3, Folder 7)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1969-1976 (Box I:3, Folder 8)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Photographs, 1974-1978 (Box I:3, Folder 9)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Documents/Objects, 1976-1978 (Box I:3, Folder 10)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Checklist, 1978 (Box I:3, Folder 11)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Press Photos, 1978 (Box I:3, Folder 12)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Lecture (Donald Kalec), 1978 November 1 (Box I:3, Folder 13)
  - House of Iran Exhibition, 1978 April-December (Box I:3, Folder 14)
  - House of Iran Exhibition, 1978 April-September (Box I:3, Folder 15)
  - House of Iran Exhibition (1978 November 14-24), 1978 May-December (Box I:3, Folder 16)
  - Turkish Show, 1978 December-1979 November (Box I:3, Folder 17)
  - Balet/Palmer/Smyth Essays, 1978 (Box I:3, Folder 18)
  - Ann Lauterbach - Poems for Washington Place Windows, 1978 January 17 (Box I:3, Folder 19)
  - Tiffany - Burlingham Information, circa 1978-1979 (Box I:3, Folder 20)
  - Tiffany Bulletin, 1979 (Box I:3, Folder 21)
  - Tiffany - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 March-1980 March (Box I:3, Folder 22)
  - Life -- "Atlantic" Wainwright Article, 1972-1979 (Box I:17, Folder 29)
  - Life -- Information and Publicity, 1978 March-1979 June (Box I:17, Folder 30)
  - LIfe -- Manual, Circa 1979-1981 (Box I:17, Folder 31)
  - Life -- Miscellaneous, 1972-1979 (Box I:17, Folder 32)
  - Life -- Photograph Titles, 1979 May (Box I:17, Folder 33)
  - Life -- Village Night, 1979 May-June (Box I:17, Folder 34)
  - American Painting -- Artist File, 1979 June-1981 April (Box I:18, Folder 1)
  - American Painting -- Fact Sheets, 1979 (Box I:18, Folder 2)
  - American Painting -- General, 1979 April-September (Box I:18, Folder 3)
  - American Painting -- Miscellaneous, 1979 March-September (Box I:18, Folder 4)
  - American Painting -- Opening September 11, 1979 May-October (Box I:18, Folder 5)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (1 of 3), 1979 October (Box I:18, Folder 6)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (2 of 3), 1979 October (Box I:18, Folder 7)
  - American Painting -- Symposium (3 of 3), 1979 October (Box I:18, Folder 8)
  - American Painting -- Traveling Reviews, etc., 1979 July-December (Box I:18, Folder 9)
  - American Symbolist -- October 23 Opening, 1979 October (Box I:18, Folder 10)
  - American Symbolist -- Corespondence, Circa 1976-1981 (Box I:18, Folder 11)
  - American Symbolist -- Correspondence (Photos), 1977 December-1980 February (Box I:18, Folder 12)
  - American Symbolist -- Correspondence (Spencer Museum), 1977 January-1980 June (Box I:18, Folder 13)
  - American Symbolist -- Fact Sheets, 1979 (Box I:18, Folder 14)
  - American Symbolist -- Miscellaneous, 1979 February-November (Box I:18, Folder 15)
  - American Symbolist -- Pivar Notes, Circa 1977-1980 (Box I:18, Folder 16)
  - American Symbolist -- Press Releases, 1979 October-November (Box I:18, Folder 17)
  - American Symbolist -- Research (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box I:18, Folder 18)
  - American Symbolist -- Research (2 of 2), 1972-1979 (Box I:18, Folder 19)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Acknowledgements, Circa 1978-1980 (Box I:18, Folder 20)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Correspondence (Hauptman-Scott), 1978 August-1980 July (Box I:18, Folder 21)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Correspondence (Luthy-ProHelvetia), 1976 August-1981 July (Box I:18, Folder 22)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Musee Cantonal Labels, Circa 1978-1981 (Box I:18, Folder 23)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Press Releases, 1980 (Box I:18, Folder 24)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Fact Sheets, 1980 (Box I:18, Folder 25)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Miscellaneous, 1977-1982 June (Box I:18, Folder 26)
  - Charles Gleyre -- Robert R. Littman Miscellaneous File, 1977 August-1981 February (Box I:18, Folder 27)
  - David Hockney -- Background, Clippings and Other Miscellaneous, 1977 May-1980 March (Box I:18, Folder 28)
  - David Hockney -- Billboard, 1980 February-June (Box I:18, Folder 29)
  - David Hockney -- Evening on Wheels Press Release, 1980 (Box I:18, Folder 30)
  - David Hockney -- Miscellaneous Information on Artist (1 of 2), 1978 March-1980 September (Box I:18, Folder 31)
  - David Hockney -- Miscellaneous Information on Artist (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box I:18, Folder 32)
  - David Hockney -- Parade/Metropolitan Opera, 1981 February-March (Box I:18, Folder 33)